人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
你被监视着
You are being watched.
■
・ 翻译  油炸电风扇
・ 翻译  惠子
■
・ 翻译  Eowyn
政府有一套秘密系统
The government has a secret system--
■
・ 翻译  敏基
・ 翻译  王小麦
一台每时每刻都在监控你的机器
a machine that spies on you every hour of every day.
■
・ 翻译  卫老哥
somehacker
幸田实果子
我设计这台机器是为了侦测恐怖行动
I designed the machine to detect acts of terror,
■
・ 翻&校  阿好
但它却看到了一切
but it sees everything--
■
压制  灰灰是菇凉
牵涉普通人的暴力罪行
violent crimes involving ordinary people.
阿包  凭陵新月  Sage  阿包  凭陵新月  Sage  阿包  凭陵新月  Sage  阿包  凭陵新月  Sage
■
时间轴
政府认为这些人无关紧要
The government considers these people irrelevant.
我们不
We don't.
受当局追捕  我们只能秘密活动
Hunted by the authorities, we work in secret.
你永远找不到我们
You will never find us.
特效
灰灰
但无论是受害人还是行凶者
But victim or perpetrator,
总监
阿好
只要你的号码被列出来  我们就会找到你
if your number's up, we'll find you.
疑犯追踪
第三季 第八集
流水的政客
The politicians come and go,
奎恩  阿伦佐
市长办公室主任
状态
未被发现
西蒙斯  派崔克
警员
状态
活动中
铁打的我们
but we'll be here forever.
比彻想追根究底
Beecher's looking for answers.
■
比彻  卡尔文
缉毒警探
状态
关系
奎恩  阿伦佐
教子
卡特  乔丝林
恋爱
我总告诉卡尔小心点
I always told Cal to be careful.
已故
警察是危险的职业
Being a cop's a dangerous job.
HR又死灰复燃
HR rebuilt itself from ashes
■
约格洛夫  彼得
约格洛夫集团总裁
状态
活动中
约格洛夫  彼得
组织  俄罗斯黑帮
职位  老大
联盟  HR
联盟状态
因为我们没抓住头儿
'cause we didn't cut off the head.
活动中
要是我们抓住了  卡尔也许还活着
If we had, Cal might still be alive.
不确定
我现在另寻他途了
I'm playing by different rules now,
拉斯里奇  米哈伊尔
化名  拉斯基  迈克尔
抓到老大为止
Until I can bring down the boss.
状态
已故
你和西蒙斯向谁汇报
Who do you and Simmons report to?
捕捉图像
图像搜索
发现匹配
奎恩  阿伦佐
市长办公室主任
状态
谁发号施令
Who calls the shots?
身份未知
法外活动
组织  HR
职位  头目
身份已知
那群王八蛋敢抢我们
Those bastards think they can steal from me?
我让叫他们自食其果
Then they're gonna reap what they sow.
芬奇  你在大扫除啊
Finch, you doing a little spring cleaning?
我倒希望是
I wish I was.
我今天早上收到了号码
I received numbers this morning.
确切讲  是三十八个号码
38 of them, to be precise.
也许机器断了哪条带
Maybe the machine blew a belt or something.
它不是割草机  里瑟先生
It's not a lawn mower, Mr. Reese.
而且它从不出错
It's also never wrong.
我还没解出所有的号码
While I haven't decoded all the numbers,
不过看起来有个共同之处
there does appear to be a common thread.
他们都是警察
They're all cops.
其中四人已确知是HR的成员
Four of them are known members of HR,
所以其他人应该也一样
leaving a high probability that the rest may be as well.
三十几名HR成员
3 dozen members of HR,
要同时进行暴力犯罪
all about to commit a violent crime?
或者他们被盯上了  HR被围攻了
Or they've been targeted, and HR is under siege.
马上要天下大乱了  里瑟先生
Things are about to get chaotic, Mr. Reese.
我已经联系肖女士来帮忙了
I've already contacted Ms. Shaw to enlist her assistance.
我去看看弗斯科在八局有没有听到
I'll see if Fusco's heard any rumblings around the Eighth
HR内讧的风声
of an HR conflict.
要是我们能确定威胁来源
If we could locate the source of the threat,
也许可以平息事态  避免升级
perhaps we could defuse the situation before it escalates.
也许
Perhaps.
对了  你最好给小熊配件背心
Meantime, you might want to get Bear here fitted for a vest.
背心
Vest?
不是你那种三件套  芬奇
Not like yours, Finch.
防弹背心
K-9 ballistic.
预备着天下大乱
For when things get chaotic.
音频拦截
主体: 弗斯科  莱奈尔
有消息吗  莱奈尔
Heard anything, Lionel?
你要是问HR的消息
If you're looking for info on HR,
最好过来看看
I got something you wanna see.
这里还好吗
Everything okay here?
-弗斯科警探  -我是斯蒂尔斯警探
- Detective Fusco. - I'm Detective Stills.
有什么能帮上忙的吗
Can we be of any assistance?
除非你们会说俄语
Not unless you speak Russian.
我只了解到  他开车过来
Best I can tell, he was driving along,
突然看到辆燃烧的车
and he came upon a burning car.
然后  要是我没理解错  有人把他敲晕了
Then--if I got this right-- someone knocked him out
抢走了他的卡车
and stole his truck.
[俄语]你好  朋友
Zdravstvuyte, my friend.
你开的是什么卡车
What kind of truck were you driving?
办公用品车  运货卡车
Office supply truck? A delivery truck?
[俄语]对
Da.
我看你继续好了  警官
I think you can take it from here, officer.
警徽真牛啊
Nice badge.
下次玩儿这手前给点儿提示行不
You wanna give me a warning next time you do something like that?
那多没惊喜啊
But that would ruin the surprise.
这个跟HR有什么关系
So what does all this have to do with HR?
知道谁开了家办公用品公司么
Know who has an office supply company?
彼得・约格洛夫
Peter Yogorov.
他用来运输毒品进城
He uses it to smuggle drugs into the city.
根据与HR的联盟
Under the HR alliance,
那些警察负责保证安全通行
the cops are supposed to provide safe passage.
你想知道HR惹了什么麻烦
Now you wanted to know why HR might be in trouble?
俄罗斯人在他们保护下丢了一车货  这麻烦如何
How about the Russians losing a truck full of contraband on their watch?
能给我们弄到那个摄像头的录像吗
Think you can get us a look at that camera feed?
能啊  我热忱为你俩效劳啊
Yeah, I love using all my favors for you guys.
你怎么想的  芬奇
What do you think, Finch?
我同意弗斯科警探的意见
I'm inclined to agree with Detective Fusco.
约格洛夫把丢货的事怪罪于HR
So Yogorov blames HR for his missing shipment.
决定要一刀两断了
Decides to sever ties.
并且盯上了三十八名HR成员
And targets 38 members of HR's rank.
局面千钧一发  里瑟先生
This situation is a powder keg, Mr. Reese.
爆发在即
It's about to explode.
那是谁点燃的导火索呢
So who lit the fuse?
获取档案
时标
整个警局都懵了
Whole department's reeling.
恐怕纽约警局再受不了更多的葬礼了
Not too sure of how many more funerals the NYPD can endure.
你知道铁尼警探
Do you have any idea what happened
和拉斯基警员之间到底怎么回事吗
between Detective Terney and Officer Laskey?
我没觉察出他们有冲突
I wasn't aware of any conflict.
甚至都不知道他们互相认识
Didn't even know they knew each other.
有人猜测这和HR有关
There's some speculation that it's HR-related.
市长担心这是有组织犯罪复苏的势头
Mayor's concerned about a resurgence in organized crime.
上次我们见面时  你说过
Last time we talked, you seemed to indicate
HR有可能和我教子的谋杀案有关
that HR might have been behind my godson's murder.
有可能
Maybe.
我不确定
I-I don't know.
我只知道想除掉HR
All I know is taking on HR...
就像是在打一场永远赢不了的仗
it's like fighting a battle that can't be won.
进一步  退三步
One step forward, three steps back.
现在  又失去了我的搭档
And now, losing my partner...
我得放弃卡尔被杀案
I need to close the book on Cal's murder.
我必须放手了
I have to move on.
我想亲自告诉你这个决定
I wanted to tell you that in person.
乔丝
Joss...
你是我认识的最敬业的警察
you're one of the most dedicated cops I know,
这座城市需要更多像你这样的警察
and the city could use more like you.
卡尔会为你的所作所为而骄傲
Cal would be very proud of everything you did.
别担心
And don't worry.
我们会查出害死他的真凶
We will find who's responsible for his death.
谢谢  阿伦佐
Thanks, Alonzo.
复制手机
随时效劳
Anytime.
我跟市长还有个会
I've got a big briefing with the mayor.
我来付账
I'll take care of this.
回头再见
I'll see you soon.
我很期待
I look forward to it.
完成
早上跟卡特聊了下
Spoke to Carter this morning.
她说她要放弃追查比彻一案了
Says she's stepping down on the Beecher case.
你相信她吗
You believe her?
就算不信  现在也不能再冒出更多尸体了
Even if I did, we can't have any more bodies dropping right now.
盯着点她  以防万一
Keep an eye on her just in case.
会的
Will do.
-约格洛夫接受新条件没  -还没
- Did Yogorov accept our new terms? - Not yet.
他想在红钩区的一个粮库见面
He wants to meet at a grain depot in Red Hook.
在西伯利亚见面都行
Meet him in Siberia if he wants.
只要能让他接受新价格
Just get him to agree to the new price.
这新人是谁
Who's the new guy?
这是米切尔
This is Mitchell.
明天晚上的货由他负责
He'll be running point on tomorrow night's shipment.
一切按计划进行
So we still on schedule?
正好该补货了
Just in time to restock the shelves.
我的人到月桂山之后会给你电话
My guy will call you when he hits Laurel Hill.
我们会护送卡车
We'll escort the trucks,
确保在城内安全通行
provide safe passage through town.
但是要额外多收10%
But it's gonna cost an extra 10%.
为什么
Why?
业务成本啊
Cost of doing business.
多出钱  就要多得好处
If I'm going to pay more, I ought to get more.
-你不觉得吗  -比如呢
- Don't you think? - Like what?
比如说  我弟弟还在里克岛监狱
My brother's still in Rikers, for one.
你们本该把我们俩都弄出来
You were supposed to get us both out.
需要时间
These things take time.
在进行中了
It's in progress.
我开始感觉我不像你的生意伙伴
I'm starting to feel less like your partner
更像是你的跟班小弟
and more like your errand boy.
我们帮你们洗钱  帮你们贩毒
We launder your money, sell your drugs,
还帮你们擦屁股
even take out your trash.
比如那个你们不敢动的缉毒警
Like that Narco cop you were too afraid to knock off.
我不是来听你抱怨的  约格洛夫
I didn't come to hear you bitch, Yogorov.
那额外的10%你给不给
You kicking in the extra 10% or what?
不给
I don't think so.
你不给  我们可不确保毒品能安全通行
You don't pay, we don't provide safe passage for the drugs.
出了事  算你的
Anything happens, it's on you.
我倒想试试
I'll take my chances.
你想怎么做
What do you wanna do?
那个我来操心
Let me worry about that.
你有新任务
I need you on a new assignment.
告诉我你没走正门
Tell me you didn't use the front door.
从不走正门
I never do.
泰勒呢
Where's Taylor?
安全的地方
Somewhere safe.
这里为什么不安全呢
Any reason he wouldn't be safe here?
因为你私下调查HR么
Like your off-the-books pursuit of H.R.?
人都得有点爱好啊
Everyone needs a hobby.
人家的爱好不会招来腐败警察
Most hobbies don't involve dirty cops staked
在公寓外面盯着
outside your apartment.
你需要的话  我帮你解决他
If you want, I can take care of him for you.
我宁愿你别去管他
I'd appreciate it if you left him alone.
无意冒犯
Respectfully,
我宁愿你这段时间也别来管我
I'd appreciate it if you left me alone for a while too.
现在这时候可不适合单打独斗  卡特
Now's not the time to fly solo, Carter.
别误解  约翰
Don't get me wrong, John.
我很感激你做过的一切  为我
I appreciate everything you've done for me
也为这个城市
and this city.
但从法律上说  你仍旧是个罪犯
But in the eyes of the law, you're still a criminal.
HR已经知道我们合作了
And HR already knows we work together.
如果他们找到证据
And if they could prove it...
不行  抱歉
No, I'm sorry.
我得一个人完成这件事
I gotta finish this alone.
好吧
All right.
做你该做的
Do what you need to do.
但HR不会乖乖束手就擒
But HR won't go down without a fight.
有力不能及的地方  给我电话
If you get in over your head, give me a call.
你们俩盯我盯成这样
With the way you guys keep tabs on me,
我能惹多大麻烦呢
how much trouble can I get in?
多加小心  乔丝
Watch your back, Joss.
看过你的档案了  卡特
Read your file, Carter.
警校全班第一
Top of your class at the academy,
各项全得高分  挺厉害
high marks across the board-- that's great.
现在  全扔一边
Now, throw it all out.
那些在街上执勤时屁用没有
None of it's worth a damn out here on the street.
稍等一下
Excuse me for one second.
马上回来
I'll be right back.
好吗  乔丝
'Sup, Joss?
你在这儿干什么  保罗
What are you doing here, Paul?
刚回城
Just got back into town.
朋友安排我在个建筑工地干活
Friend hooked me up with a construction crew.
看你才脱军服  又穿警服啊
I see you traded in one uniform for another.
看来你
Guess you, uh,
就是喜欢抓坏人
always had a thing for hunting bad guys.
没回答我的问题
None of that answers my question.
想看看你过得如何
Wanted to see how you were getting along, you know?
看我们儿子怎么样
See how our son was doing.
你凭什么消失了两年后跳出来
You think you can just show up after two years
就要见泰勒
and ask to see Taylor?
乔丝  情况现在好多了  好吗
Look, Joss, things are better now, okay?
我好多了
I'm better.
这么说你去退伍军人事务部了
So that means you went to the V.A.?
退伍军人事务部
The V.A.?
我不需要那些心理医生分析我
I don't need some head shrinker analyzing me.
好吗  乔丝
All right, Joss?
我只是需要些时间  理清头绪
I just needed some time to just clear my head.
没那么简单  保罗
It's not that simple, Paul.
我看到战争对你的影响了
I saw the toll combat took on you.
你还觉得我很危险  是吗
You still think I'm a danger, don't you?
-乔丝  我从没碰过你们一根指头  -不
- Joss, I never laid a hand on either one of y'all. - No.
我只是发现你睡在厨房地板上
I'd just find you asleep on the kitchen floor
抱着一把枪  而我们儿子就在隔壁
cradling a gun, with our son in the next room.
不会有下一次了
That's not gonna happen again.
你没错
You're right.
不会了
It won't.
因为如果你不去寻求帮助
Because if you don't get help,
就永远别想再接触你儿子
you'll never have a relationship with your son.
在那之前
And until then,
我想你最好离我们远一点
I think it's best you stay away from both of us.
收到你的留言了  弗斯科
I got your messages, Fusco.
十条都收到了
All ten of 'em.
我听说拉斯基的事了
I heard what happened to Laskey.
你还好吗
How you holding up?
失去搭档总是令人痛苦
It's never an easy thing, losing a partner.
叫人想知道
Kinda makes you wonder
那晚他们俩到底发生了什么事
what really went down between those two that night.
不太想知道
Not sure I wanna know.
知道我怎么想吗
You know what I think?
我觉得当时还有别人在
I think someone else was there.
我觉得是有人杀了他们两个人
I think someone shot them both
布置了现场
and staged the scene.
唯一的问题是  谁
The only question is, who?
我不知道  弗斯科
I don't know, Fusco.
但不管发生什么事
But whatever happened,
我都不想参与
I don't want any part of it.
是铁尼告诉你
Terney was the one who told you
HR杀死了你男朋友
HR had your boyfriend killed.
现在他跟你那菜鸟搭档死一块儿了
Now he's dead along with your rookie partner?
你就不想知道原因吗
I mean, don't you wanna know why?
我意识到了
Something I realized:
有时不值得为了原因而冒险
It's not always worth the risk to know why.
看来不值得
I guess not.
会好起来的  弗斯科
It'll be all right, Fusco.
这段时间低调点
Just lay low for a while.
是啊
Yeah.
我得回去了
Listen, I gotta get back.
别跟我见外啊
Don't stay a stranger, all right?
是我
It's me.
我要你去拜访一个人
I need you to pay someone a visit.
刚收到消息
Just got word.
货已经过州境了
Our shipment's crossed state lines.
目前  没遇到麻烦
So far, no signs of trouble.
真叫我怀疑咱一开始干嘛非需要那些警察
Makes me wonder why we ever needed cops for this in the first place.
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
你知道你最大的罪行是什么吗  彼得
You know what crime you're most guilty of, Peter?
让这人给你下厨
Letting this man cook for you.
挺沉的吧
Those look heavy.
放松
Relax.
我要想你死
If I wanted you dead,
肯定会比这有创意
I'd be a little more creative than this.
没想到你居然还在城里
I'm surprised you're still in town.
还以为你躺在沙滩上
Figured you be on a beach somewhere,
品鉴美酒  疗伤自怜呢
sipping Mai Tais and licking your wounds.
我可不能走啊
I just can't leave yet.
要尽情欣赏
Not with front-row seats to
你和HR的狗血大戏呢
this little drama playing out between you and HR.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
历史又在重演了  彼得
The wheels of history are turning again, Peter.
相信我
Take my word for it.
警察不能控制你  就会背叛你
If the cops can't control you, they'll betray you.
如同他们之前对我
Just like they did me.
但不同的是  你还有机会扭转乾坤
But unlike me, you still have a chance to do something about this.
杀父仇人的谆谆教导啊
Words of wisdom from the man who killed my father.
说说我干嘛要听你的
Tell me why I should listen to you.
敌人的敌人啊
Enemy of my enemy.
我不能放过让HR受罪的机会啊
I just can't pass up a chance to watch HR suffer.
这是什么
What's this?
礼物
A gift.
炖15分钟  加醋搅拌
Let that simmer for 15 minutes, then stir with vinegar.
约格洛夫收到东西了
Yogorov got the package.
但他能不能领悟就另说了
Whether he received the message is another story.
他很快会明白的
He'll understand soon enough.
直接让我宰了他  大家都省事
Save everyone a lot of trouble if you'd let me kill him.
没必要
That won't be necessary.
实际上
In fact,
接下来这几天  你最好低调点
you might want to keep a low profile for the next couple days.
正有此意
Already planning on it.
无论你有何计划  警官
And whatever you're up to, officer,
祝你好运
I wish you the best of luck.
感觉你会很需要
I have a feeling you're gonna need it.
给谁打电话
Who was on the phone?
一个欠我人情的人
Someone who owes me a favor.
都在这了吗
It's all there?
应有尽有  几乎全包  相信我
Everything but the kitchen sink. Tried it, didn't fit.
我很感激你没告诉他们俩
I appreciate you not telling the guys about this.
不能让男生把乐子全占了
Boys can't have all the toys.
拿着这些家伙  你是准备要大干一场啊
You're fixing to have quite a party with all this stuff.
确定不需要帮忙吗
You sure you don't need an assist?
那37毫米口径的货  不容易上手哟
The 37 mil can be tricky.
谢了
Thanks.
还是我自己来吧
But I can take it from here.
■
追踪车辆
海滨办公用品
车辆内载
50个打印机墨盒
100个活页夹
200令纸
50千克可卡因
50千克海洛因
50000板摇头丸
净值:
1280万
坦白说  里瑟先生
Honestly, Mr. Reese,
看着真像你的手笔
this looks like something you would do.
必须承认  我真希望有受邀
Gotta admit, I wish I was invited.
我详细调查了38名HR成员中的30名
After digging into 30 out of the 38 HR numbers,
没哪个[男]人有录像上那种身手
not a single man possesses the talents displayed in that footage.
我都不确定是男人
I'm not so sure it was a man.
来看下这个
Come take a look at this.
身高  身形
Height, build--
这位袭击者应该是女人
I think our assailant might be a woman.
女人带着防毒面具放火烧车  抢劫毒品
A woman sets a car on fire and attacks a drug shipment wearing a gas mask?
你想起谁来了  里瑟先生
Who does that remind you of, Mr. Reese?
你们俩看什么呢
What are you guys looking at?
好吧  你们俩古古怪怪的
All right, you're being weird.
你的杰作吗
This your handiwork?
她还真会用37毫米口径的货
I guess she does know her way around a 37 mil.
肖女士  你知道此事
Ms. Shaw, you know something about this?
我知道有人需要武器
I know someone needed firepower.
里瑟一大把
Reese had plenty,
我就替他捐了点
so I made a donation on his behalf.
等等
Wait.
那是我的榴弹发射器
That's my grenade launcher?
我的天  那是卡特警探  是吧
Oh, my God, that's Detective Carter, isn't it?
你的社交圈可不广
Your social circle isn't terribly wide.
她说了不想你们插手
She told me she didn't want you guys involved.
因为我们会劝她收手
Because we would have tried to talk her out of it.
目前为止  她对HR的调查
Until now, her investigation into HR
还局限在法律层面
has fallen on the legal side of things.
但这个
But this...
挑拨他们对抗俄罗斯人
pitting them against the Russians?
你们俩盯住所有的号码
You two get eyes on every one of those numbers.
我们怎么分身到四十个地方呢
And how exactly can we be 40 places at once?
我不管
I don't care.
如果他们发现是卡特做的
If they find out Carter's behind this,
只会跳出一个号码  她的
only one number's coming up-- hers.
喂
Yes?
早上好  阿伦佐
Good morning, Alonzo.
你怎么知道这个号码的
How did you get this number?
在一次性手机上找到的
Found it on the burner phone
你手下昨晚劫走我的货车时丢下的
your man dropped when he made off with my supply truck last night.
听说你那批货出事儿了  我很遗憾
I was sorry to hear about what happened to your shipment,
但我不是很明白你的意思
but I'm not exactly sure what you're implying.
你劫了我  老东西
You ripped me off, old man.
带着你的玩具回家玩儿了
Taking your toys and going home.
只不过那不是你该拿的
Except they weren't your toys to take.
我就当作是
I'm going to pretend
你一时判断失察吧
you're having a momentary lapse in judgment.
你被抢了  现在脑子不清醒
You got robbed, and now you're not thinking straight.
那我就把话挑明了说
Then let me be extra clear right now.
我正看着HR高层的名字和照片
I'm looking at names and pictures of top-level HR members.
还我毒品
Return my drugs,
不然你的人就别想回家吃晚饭
or your men don't make it home for dinner.
乔丝
Joss?
芬奇  我没找到卡特
Finch, I haven't found Carter,
但我想我知道谁是HR的头儿了
but I think I know who the head of HR is.
我想我也知道了
And I believe I know as well.
我刚刚解出了最后一个号码
I just decoded the last number.
阿伦佐・奎恩
Alonzo Quinn.
说得通
Makes sense.
市长办公室主任的职位非常适合
The mayor's chief of staff would be in a prime position
暗中领导HR
to lead HR from the shadows.
他也是下令杀害比彻的人
He's also the man who ordered Beecher's death.
这对卡特来说  这仇比我们之前所料要深多了
This is more personal for Carter than we thought.
那你最好竭尽全力找到她
Then you'd better do everything in your power to find her.
我看见你在找我
I see you're looking for me.
乔丝
Joss?
你在哪儿
Where are you?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you that.
但我知道你在哪儿
But I know exactly where you are.
还以为你答应要保持距离了呢
Thought you promised to keep your distance.
那是在我知道你挑起战争之前
That was before I knew you were starting a war.
我们知道奎恩和他对卡尔做的事了
We know about Quinn and what he did to Cal.
那你也该知道为什么不能让他逍遥在外
Then you know why he can't get away with it.
相信我
Take it from me.
复仇解决不了问题
Revenge isn't the answer.
告诉我你在哪儿  拜托  让我帮你
Tell me where you are. Please just let me help you.
你曾经请求我相信你会做应做之事
You once asked me to trust you to do what needed to be done.
现在我有同样请求
Now I'm asking the same of you.
说吧
Talk to me.
没人知道谁袭击了俄罗斯人的车
No one knows who hit the Russian truck.
犯罪中心的监控录像"恰好"失踪
Video footage from the RTCC is conveniently missing.
一定是西装男捣的鬼
This has "man in the suit" written all over it.
坦白说  我不管是谁劫了约格洛夫的货
Frankly, I don't care who stole Yogorov's cargo.
如果他终止了跟我们的联盟合作
If he's considering an end to our alliance,
那他就是首要麻烦
he's a major liability.
他在威胁我们的人
He's threatening our people.
要我说联盟已经完了
I'd say the alliance if finished.
彼得・约格洛夫没种对付我们
Peter Yogorov doesn't have the stones to come after us.
老大  刚才怎么了
Boss, what the hell just happened?
刚刚有人朝我办公室里开枪了
Someone just took a shot at me in my office.
约格洛夫
Yogorov.
既然他忘恩负义  别怪我翻脸无情
He wants to bite the hand that feeds, he can starve.
围捕他的头目们  带到红钩区
Round up his top ranks and take them on out to Red Hook.
杀掉他们  埋了他们
Kill 'em and bury 'em.
把约格洛夫带来给我
But bring Yogorov to me.
我要亲自处理那杂种
I'll deal with that son of a bitch myself.
你去找卡特警探的时候
While you were looking for Detective Carter,
我收到了更多号码
I received more numbers.
看来HR要反击俄罗斯人  以牙还牙
It appears that HR has responded to the Russian threat in kind.
看来这早晚是要
Guess it was only a matter of time
升级成一场大战了
until this escalated into an all-out war.
别介意我不合时机的幽默
If you'll forgive my gallows humor,
我押HR赢
I'll put my money on HR.
为什么这么说
Why do you say that?
因为他们那边有一些东西
Because they have something on their side
俄罗斯人没有  里瑟先生
that the Russians don't, Mr. Reese.
法律
The law.
抓捕约格洛夫的人
Grab Yogorov's men.
悄悄行动
Keep it quiet.
街上别见血
No blood on the streets.
把手放在我能看见的地方
Hands where I can see them.
下车
Get out of the car.
约洛夫  尼古莱
被捕
尼古莱  你他妈在哪儿
Nikolai, where the hell are you?
多加小心  HR对我们动手了
Watch your back. HR's moving against us.
头五个进门的人可以提前退休了
First five guys through that door get early retirement!
有退休金吗
That come with a pension?
我记得你
I remember you.
好啊  省了自我介绍了
Good, we can skip the introduction.
HR已经围捕了你所有的小弟
HR already rounded up all your boys.
你是最后的幸存者
You're the last little Indian.
现在  他们正在赶过来
And right now, they're on their way here
来杀你
to kill you.
你要想活命
So if you wanna live,
就跟我走
you're coming with me.
上次我跟你走  你逮捕了我
Last time I went with you, you arrested me.
所谓旧习难改啊
Guess old habits die hard.
泰勒
Taylor!
Taylor?
你还好吧
You okay?
我们好极了
We're great.
对吧  小家伙
Aren't we, little man, hmm?
对不起  他突然出现
I'm sorry. He just showed up.
没关系  谢谢你打电话给我
It's all right, thanks for calling.
保罗  能跟你出去说句话吗
Paul, can I talk to you outside?
在这说不行吗
Why not here?
儿子已经长大了  可以听听你要说什么
I mean, the boy's old enough to hear what you have to say.
带我儿子回他的房间
Take my son into his room.
好  来吧  泰勒
Sure. Come on, Taylor.
你搞什么鬼
The hell are you doing,
想被我抓起来吗
besides giving me a good reason to lock you up?
听着  乔丝
Look, Joss.
男孩的生活中需要父亲
A boy needs a father in his life.
愿意承认自己需要帮助的父亲
A father who's willing to admit when he needs help.
你知道吗
You know what?
你没见过我经历的战争
You didn't see combat like I did.
你只需待在基地  跟恐怖分子聊聊天
You spent your time back on a base, chatting up terrorists.
等你回到家了  就没事了
And then when you came home, you were fine.
你以为对我就那么容易吗
You think it was that easy for me?
我也有问题
I had problems too.
但我想办法解决了
But I found ways to handle them.
我自己解决了
Look, just because I did it by myself
不代表你也得自己解决
doesn't mean you have to.
好吧  我猜猜
Okay, so let me guess.
我应该去  退伍军人事务部  是吧
I should go... talk to the V.A., right?
我说过  我不会去的
I told you, I'm not gonna do that.
是啊  因为你总是逃避问题
That's right, because you run from your problems.
我没逃避
I'm not running!
你要对我开枪吗  乔丝
You gonna shoot me now, Joss?
滚出我的房子
Get out of my house.
乔丝
Joss--
-谢谢  -没事
- Thank you. - Yeah.
真抱歉让你听到那些
I'm sorry you had to hear that.
爸爸怎么了
What's wrong with daddy?
有时候他会很暴躁
Sometimes he gets mad.
但他不知道原因
And he doesn't know why.
他会好起来吗
Will he get better?
我不知道  宝贝
I don't know, baby.
但是
But hey...
只要我们还有彼此
as long as we got each other,
你跟我一定会没事的
you and I are gonna be fine.
好吗
Okay?
过来
Come here.
这就是你所谓的保护
This your idea of protection?
贝德福德的警局
A sheriff station in Bedford?
我以酒驾罪名关押你  用的名字是乔・曼可
I booked you as a DUI under the name Joe Manco.
这至少能让你多活几个小时
Should keep you alive for a few hours, at least.
对开枪打HR头儿的人  我只能做到这样了
The best I could do for the guy who took a shot at the head of HR.
我没开枪
I didn't take a shot at anyone.
那些腐败警察  彼得
Thing about dirty cops, Peter...
他们可不太看重证据
they're not big on evidence.
你认识这个人吗
Do you recognize this man?
几个月前被打死的警察
That cop got shot a few months back.
他名叫卡尔・比彻
His name's Cal Beecher.
他是阿伦佐・奎恩的教子
He was Alonzo Quinn's godson.
提醒我给他送花
Remind me to send flowers.
彼得  我知道奎恩是HR的头儿
Peter, I know Quinn's the head of HR.
我也知道  就是他下令要你的人
And I know he ordered your men
去干掉比彻
to carry out the hit on Beecher.
就算是真的
Even if that were true...
也永远无法证明
never be able to prove it.
也许不能
Maybe not.
但话说回来
But then again...
我跟踪HR和俄国人几个月了
I've been following HR and the Russians for months.
我有足够的证据拿下几乎所有人
I've gathered enough evidence to put almost everybody away,
包括你
including you.
那我们还谈什么呢
So then why are we talking?
因为今天是你的幸运日
Because it's your lucky day.
比起你的脑袋  我更想要奎恩的
I want Quinn's head more than I want yours.
抱歉
Sorry.
我宁可烂在牢里  也不愿被看成叛徒
I'd rather rot in prison than be labeled a rat.
不论我身处何地  总是先准备好退路
Every room I go in, I always look for the exits.
我曾当过兵
I was a soldier.
改不了这个习惯
Can't turn it off.
所以当我说你只有一条退路时  相信我吧
So trust me when I tell you you only have one way out of this.
那就是扳倒奎恩
And that's Quinn going down.
只要他还逍遥在外
He stays out there,
不论我抓住了谁
doesn't matter who else I arrest,
他最终都会冲你来
he'll be coming for you eventually.
我能保护好自己
I can take care of myself.
我理解
I respect that.
真的
I really do.
但你弟弟也一样吗
But can you say the same for your brother?
你想过HR为什么让他待在里克岛监狱吗
You ever wonder why HR's kept him in Rikers?
当人质
Leverage.
有好几名候审的腐败警察
There are about half a dozen corrupt cops awaiting trial
现在和你弟弟关在同一牢区
on the same cell block as your brother right now.
你签了这份供词
You sign this statement...
我能安排拉兹罗
I could get Lazlo moved to safer facilities
数小时内转到安全地方
within the next few hours.
如何呢
So what's it gonna be?
把那该死的供词给我
Just show me the damn statement.
然后呢
Now what?
我得申请一份奎恩的逮捕令
I get an arrest warrant for Quinn.
你确定能找到可靠的法官吗
You sure you got a judge you can trust with that?
奎恩喜欢到处洒钱
Quinn liked to spread that money around.
我们可帮他赚大发了
We made him a lot of it.
这几天我查了不少法官
Spent the last few days vetting judges.
选出了几名
Narrowed it down to a couple.
我的供词
My statement,
加上你搜集的证据
the evidence you got,
结果这事成不成全得靠撞大运
and this whole thing comes down to blind luck.
帮个忙  警官
Do me a favor, Officer.
选择明智点
Choose wisely.
否则的话
Because if you don't,
你  我  我弟弟
then you, me, and my brother...
都死定了
are all dead.
吓了我个半死  卡特
Scared me half to death, Carter.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
不能冒险
Can't take any chances.
是啊  神奇小子告诉我你在干嘛了
Yeah, Wonder Boy told me what you're up to.
你这叫低调啊
This your idea of laying low?
我得制造点混乱
I had to make a bit of a mess.
所以才需要见你
That's why I needed to see you.
是吗
Yeah?
我不知道为什么
I'm not sure why.
我一开始不明白
I couldn't figure out at first
为什么你不肯告诉我
why you didn't read me into this thing.
为什么你要背着我
Why you cut me out.
后来我意识到你还是不信任我
Then I realized you still don't trust me.
我理解
I get it.
有些事儿做过了  就永远洗不白
I guess there's a certain stink you really can't wash off.
不是这样的  弗斯科
That's not it, Fusco.
但我知道你好不容易
But I know how hard it was for you
才从HR脱身出来
to get out from underneath HR.
一旦出错
Anything goes wrong,
他们第一个找的就会是你
you're the first guy they're gonna come for.
我只是想保护你
I was trying to protect you.
保护我
Protect me?
通过瞒着我吗
By keeping me in the dark?
我还当我们是搭档
I thought we were partners.
我们是  所以我才来
We are. That's why I'm here now.
这是什么
What's this?
保管箱的钥匙
It's to a safety deposit box
在霍博肯的一州银行
at the One State bank in Hoboken.
里面是我搜集到的全部HR活动
Inside is everything I collected on HR.
录音  资金流向  一切
Recordings, money trails, everything.
我要去申请奎恩的逮捕令
I'm about to get an arrest warrant for Quinn.
然后呢
Then what?
然后我就逮捕他
Then I'm gonna arrest him.
但万一出事
But if anything happens...
我要你保管这个
I need you to hold on to that.
-不行  -什么不行
- No. - "No" what?
你不能就这么跑来
No way you're gonna come here
说一堆"万一出事"之类的屁话
with this "if anything happens to me" crap.
莱奈尔  你是世界上唯一一个
Lionel, you're the only person in the world
我可以托付的人
I trust with this.
而且
Plus...
你是我最好的搭档
you're the best partner I ever had.
如果你觉得自己跑过来说了这番话后
If you think I'm gonna let you take down Quinn by yourself
我会任你一个人去单挑奎恩
after coming here and saying something like that,
你是打错算盘了
you got another thing coming.
好吧
Okay.
用你的车  但我来开
We'll take your car, but I'm driving.
你最好穿上防弹背心
You might want to get your vest.
我去拿
Let me grab it.
还有  把你的12号口径手枪也带上
You know what? Grab your 12-gauge too.
好
All right.
抱歉  弗斯科
Sorry, Fusco.
但这事我必须一个人做
But I gotta do this one alone.
这一切本可避免
All this could have been avoided
偏偏你老大要杀我老大
if your boss hadn't tried to kill mine.
卡特一心想抓奎恩
Carter's so determined to get Quinn,
都不顾间接伤害了
She's forgotten about collateral damage.
准备好了吗  肖
You ready, Shaw?
一个问题
One question--
我们从警察坏蛋手里救下俄罗斯坏蛋后
once we save the bad Russians from the bad cops,
要怎么处置他们呢
what exactly are we gonna do with them?
动手吧
Let's finish this.
联调局  这里谁负责
FBI! Who's in charge here?
斯坦・米切尔警探
Detective Stan Mitchell.
我们得到线报说俄罗斯黑帮在这儿交易
We got a tip the Russians were making a deal out here.
过来抓捕
We came to bust it up.
卡特
Carter.
我们也收到线报了
You know, we got a tip as well.
一群腐败警察
Bunch of corrupt cops
为了大量遗失毒品要杀掉俄罗斯人
were gonna kill some Russians over a pile of missing drugs.
介意我们看看你的后备箱吗
Mind if we look in your trunk?
希望你有个好律师  警探
Hope you got a good lawyer, detective.
看来这边的活儿搞定了
Guess our work here is done.
你找到她了吗  莱奈尔
Did you find her, Lionel?
她找到我了  但她
She found me. But she, uh...
我猜猜
Let me guess.
她甩掉你了
She ditched you.
她要一个人做
She's going alone on this one.
她不想别人帮忙
She doesn't want any help.
他们若知道她做的事儿  会杀了她  约翰
They'll kill her if they figure out what she's up to, John.
那我们最好找到她
We'd better find her then.
我们分头行动
Let's split up.
分散等芬奇找到她所在的位置
Spread out in case Finch comes up with her location.
你好
Hello.
莫纳汉法官  我是乔丝・卡特
Judge Monahan? It's Joss Carter.
抱歉这么晚来电
I apologize for calling so late,
但我希望你今晚能给我签发一份逮捕令
but I was hoping you could grant me an arrest warrant tonight.
明天早上不行吗
It can't be done in the morning?
恐怕不行
I'm afraid not.
我有一份证词
I have a sworn statement
证明市政厅的一名要员
implicating a prominent member of City Hall
牵涉重大犯罪及腐败集团
in a major crime and corruption ring.
这事你和地检官说过了吗
Have you spoken to the D.A. about this?
会说  明天一早就说
I will, first thing in the morning.
但现在  我需要逮捕令
But right now, I need the warrant.
我明白
I understand.
尽快过来吧
Get here as soon as you can.
先生  我是安德鲁・莫纳汉法官
Sir, this is Judge Andrew Monahan.
抱歉打扰你休息
I'm sorry to bother you at home.
我刚接到一个电话  你也许想知道
I just received a call you might want to be aware of.
你认识一名叫乔丝・卡特的警员吗
Do you know a police officer by the name of Joss Carter?
你通知我是对的
You were right to contact me.
告诉我她说了什么
Tell me everything she told you.
乔丝
Joss!
没穿制服
No uniform.
你升职当警探了
You made detective.
你想要怎样  保罗
What you need, Paul?
我不是来要求什么的
I didn't come here to ask you for anything.
我只是
I just...
想给你看看这个
just wanted to show you this.
退伍军人事务部
保罗・卡特
好样的
Good for you.
-你看起来好多了  -是好多了
- You look better. - I am.
没完全康复  但有进展
I mean, not all the way, but some.
心理咨询真够呛
The counseling's kicking my ass.
有许多我不愿再回想的事
Lot of stuff I didn't wanna relive--
我做过的事  伤过的人
things I did, people I hurt.
是啊  保罗  我
Yeah, Paul, I--
不不不  我懂
No, no, no. I know.
没办法回头了
There's no going back.
我现在明白了
I see that now.
但他们一直告诉我  我得找个办法前行
But they keep telling me I have to find a way forward,
找个目标
a purpose.
我现在正在努力
That's what I'm working on now.
我只是想让你知道
I just wanted you to know that.
如果泰勒和你有什么需要我做的
If there's ever anything I can do for Taylor, for both of you,
我的电话
here's my number.
谢谢你听我说完  乔丝
Thanks for hearing me out, Joss.
好了
All right.
喂
Hello?
保罗  是我
Paul, it's me.
乔丝
Joss.
我让他接电话
Let me get him for you.
其实  我有话跟你说
Actually, I needed to tell you something.
怎么了
What's up?
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢你照顾他
For taking care of him.
还好他有你依靠
It's good he can rely on you.
本就该如此  乔丝
That's how it's supposed to be, Joss.
永远都该如此
That's how it always should have been.
对吧
All right?
等等  有人想和你说话
Hold on, somebody wants to talk to you.
妈
Mom.
宝贝
Baby.
在那边如何
How's it going over there?
很好  爸爸本想做焙盘炖菜
Good. Dad tried to make a casserole.
结果还是叫披萨外卖了
We ended up ordering pizza.
真是没救了
Y'all are hopeless.
你还好吗
You okay?
当然  没事
Yeah! Fine.
正在开车
Just driving and, uh...
我想说  对不起
I wanted to say I'm sorry.
为什么
For what?
对我来说
To me...
你还是我的小家伙  知道吗
you're still my little dude, you know?
有时候  我忘了  你其实已经长大了
Sometimes I-I forget you're practically all grown up.
过去的这八个月
These last eight months,
我一直偷偷摸摸  瞒着你
I've been secretive, keeping you in the dark.
你在保护我  我懂
You're protecting me. I get it.
但无论你做什么
But whatever you're doing,
你知道自己不用一个人孤军奋战  是吧
you know you don't have to do it alone, right?
有你挺我  是吧
You got my back, don't you?
永远  而且不只是我
Always. And not just me.
很多人关心你
Lots of people care about you.
如果你需要帮助  开口就行
If you ever need any help, all you have to do is ask.
你知道的  是吧
You know that, right?
我爱你  宝贝儿子
I love you, baby boy.
明早打给你
I'll call you tomorrow.
我也爱你  妈
I love you too, mom.
好
Okay.
莫纳汉法官
Judge Monahan,
非常感谢您
thank you so much for--
我们速战速决  好吧
Let's get this over with, shall we?
当然  我这么晚过来
Absolutely. I wouldn't be here this late
实在因为事关重大  法官大人
if it wasn't important, your honor.
这逮捕令是关键
See, this warrant is the key to our--
他指的不是逮捕令  乔丝
He wasn't talking about the warrant, Joss.
听说你在找我
Heard you were looking for me.
就想帮你省点麻烦
Figured I'd save you the trouble.
免了那堆莎士比亚的唧唧歪歪吧
I'll spare you the Shakespeare quote.
其实  这正是你的问题所在
You know, I think that's your problem.
你当自己是某出伟大悲剧的主角
You see yourself as a protagonist in some great tragedy.
要一个人孤身挑战这个世界
Determined to face the world alone.
不惜因此送命
Even if it gets you killed.
"生存还是毁灭"  贱人
"To be or not to be," bitch.
走
Move.
无论如何
For what it's worth,
我曾希望能避免有这么一天
I had hoped that we could have avoided this day.
至少有种亲自杀了我
At least have the balls to pull the trigger yourself.
别像对你教子那样叫别人动手
Don't outsource me like you did your own godson.
我也不想他那样
I don't relish what happened to him,
但有时候为了大局  牺牲在所难免
but sometimes sacrifices are necessary for the greater good.
我错就错在没把你和卡尔一起干掉
My mistake was not having you killed along with Cal.
那你俩就都不用一个人孤零零死去了
Then neither of you would have had to die alone.
你说得对
You were right.
我错了
I was wrong.
我还以为能一个人扳倒你
I thought I could take you down alone.
总是有信任问题
Always did have trust issues.
想要做得光明正大  干净清白
Tried to do it clean.
照片  录音  证词
Photos, recordings, sworn testimony.
但我意识到
But then I realized
你太肮脏腐败
you're just too dirty.
我查到哪里
Everywhere I turned,
你都有朋友帮你脱身
you had friends ready to help you out.
而我却是一个人
And I was alone.
所以
So...
我也叫了自己的朋友
I called some friends of my own.
你们都听到了吗  各位
You get all that, fellas?
她没带窃听
She's not wired.
这是奇迹时代  小子们
It's a brave new world, boys.
你们不看报纸吗
Don't you read the papers?
人家可以窃听你们的手机
Anyone can listen in on your phone.
即使关机了也一样
Even when it's turned off.
我错就错在没把你和卡尔一起干掉
My mistake was not having you killed along with Cal.
那你俩就都不用一个人孤零零死去了
Then neither of you would have had to die alone.
现在  里瑟先生
Now, Mr. Reese.
所有人  趴下
Everybody, down!
滚进来  快
Get your ass up here, now!
多谢你的帮助
Thanks for the help.
多谢你的电话
Thanks for the call.
要把他带去哪儿
Where are we taking him?
下城区的联邦大厦
Fed building downtown.
联调局可能是我们唯一能信任的了
The FBI may be the only ones we can trust.
沿途一堆的腐败警察
Lot of dirty cops between here and there.
这会是你人生中的最后一个错误
This will be the last mistake you ever make.
纽约警察
NYPD!
举起手
Get your hands on your--
他们在哪儿
Where the hell are they?
走了
Gone.
死火了
It's dead.
他打中了发动机
He shot out the engine.
他没打中摄像头
He didn't shoot your camera.
把这张悬赏出去
Get this out on the wire.
只给我们的人
Our people only.
不光是警察
Not just the ones in blue.
我要道上所有的黑帮都拿到这张照片
I want every criminal outfit on the street to have this picture.
西装男今晚必死
The man in the suit dies tonight.